Coming up in this lesson you'll implement a character-wise RNN.
在本课中 你将实现一个字符型 RNN
That is, the network will learn about some text
也就是说 此网络将通过每一次学习
one character at a time and then generate new text one character at a time.
一个字符来学习一些文本 然后再一次一个字符生成新的文本
Let's say, we want to generate new Shakespeare plays.
假设 我们想生成新的莎士比亚台词
As an example, to be or not to be.
例如“To be or not to be”
We'd pass the sequence into our RNN one character at a time.
我们将一次一个字符将此序列传入我们的 RNN
Once trained the network will generate new text by predicting
训练后 此网络将根据它看到的字符
the next character based on the characters it's already seen.
预测下一个字符 以此来生成新的文本
So then to train this network we wanted
那么要训练此网络 我们要
to predict the next character in the input sequence.
预测输入序列中的下一个字符
In this way the network will learn to produce a sequence of
这样 网络将能够生成与原文本
characters that look like the original text.
大致一样的一系列字符
Let's consider what the architecture of this network will look like.
我们来看看这个网络的架构是什么样的
First, let's unroll the RNN so we can see how this all works as a sequence.
首先我们展开这个 RNN 看看它的序列的工作原理
Here, we have our input layer where we'll
这里是输入层 我们
pass in the characters as one hot encoded vectors.
在此将字符作为独热编码向量传入
These vectors go to the hidden layer.
这些向量进入隐藏层
The hidden layer is built with LSTM cells where
隐藏层由 LSTM 单元构建 其中
the hidden state and cell state pass from one cell to the next in the sequence.
隐藏状态和单元状态从序列中的一个单元传递到下一个单元
In practice, we'll actually use multiple layers of LSTM cells.
在实践中 我们实际上会使用多层 LSTM 单元
You just stack them up like this.
只需像这样将它们堆叠起来即可
The output of these cells go to the output layer.
这些单元的输出将进入输出层
The output layer is used to predict to the next character.
输出层用于预测下一个字符
We want the probabilities for each character the same way
我们希望用你在卷积网络中进行
you did image classification with the cabinet.
图像分类时使用的相同方式 来获得每个字符的概率
That means that we want a Softmax activation on the output.
这意味着我们要对输出使用 Softmax 激活
Our target here will be the input sequence but shifted over one
我们在此的目标是输出输入序列 但要后移一个
so that each character is predicting the next character in the sequence.
以便每个字符能预测序列中的下一个字符
Again, we'll use cross entropy loss for training with gradient descent.
再次 我们将使用交叉熵损失和梯度下降法进行训练
When this network is trained up we can pass in one character
此网络训练好后 我们便可以传入一个字符
and get out a probability distribution for the likely next character.
并获得可能的下一个字符的概率分布
Then we can sample from that distribution to get the next character.
然后从该分布中取样以得到下一个字符
Then we can take that character,
然后我们传入
pass it in and get another one.
这一个字符并获得另一个
We keep doing this and eventually we'll build up some completely new text.
重复这样做 最终我们就会获得一些全新的文本
We'll be training this network on the text from Anna Karenina,
我们将使用我最爱的一本书
one of my favorite books.
《安娜·卡列尼娜》中的文本来训练网络
It's in the public domain so it's free to use however you want.
这本书属于公共领域 所以你可以随意使用
Also, it's an amazing novel.
而且 这也是一本了不起的小说